You
Where are you going uh practice what but I thought that all of your matches ended yesterday
No, no, no, no, no, no
Kurakawa Tashiro hi guys hey daichi
Why are you playing basketball because this is the basketball team's gym
Whoa
What about the volleyball team where the heck is everyone else? What do you mean? Where is everyone else?
What do I mean
You're the only person on the volleyball team
That's sucked the worst possible way to start off the new year
Oh
I got here way too early
We're not supposed to meet up for another 30 minutes
Oh
Hey
um hey guys
did i maybe get the time wrong for this oh no no not at all best wishes and a happy new year to you
and a happy new year to you
we've never done a new year shrine visit as a team have we that would mean this is literally our new
new year shrine visit which of course means that what we did last year was just a regular shrine
visit so next year will be a new regular year shrine visit hey come on are you guys even
listening suga you seriously need to calm down now and you could at least react a little bit
what too busy trying to breathe uh what
i'm gonna go pick a fortune yeah me too wow i haven't done that in years
i'll see huh i'd pick a bad one and get depressed don't be ridiculous you're gonna be just fine
seriously that's like talent so it's kind of like your good luck is having nothing but super bad
luck all the time you should just embrace it it's like ranking 11th place on horoscope luck
shut up all right what the hell did you two get then future good well that's even more boring than
just bad luck
come to think of it i think i heard when you go to a shrine you
should be thankful for everyday blessings instead of just asking the gods for like favors what but
all i did was ask for a ton of stuff like for our matches and for my future i even asked them for
good health for the old dog that lives next door he's been looking pretty bad oh the gods are gonna
think i'm just some entitled jerkwad i would imagine the gods are more forgiving than that i mean you
really can't resist praying to them for some help winning a few matches can you
asking the gods for help doesn't automatically mean they'll let you win
well kyoko that's uh really kyoko you're going to say that right now don't worry guys
we'll be fine even without the gods help i'm certain we will
so
hmm
It was just a dream.
I know that.
I know it was just a dream, but...
You know, just in case.
Hmm.
You've got to learn, Hinata!
God damn it!
Just call me Tanaka, the Battle Master!
Okay, get ready! Look out!
Take this!
That's nothing!
Sorry!
Oh, Daichi!
Hey, Daichi!
It's the captain!
Hey!
Sup!
What are all you guys doing up here?
You know the gym isn't open today.
I swung by after my New Year's shrine visit and they were all here!
I just sort of ended up here during my run.
I was just trying to get away from my drunk sister.
I wanted a worthy foe.
What are you people, tuna?
Huh?
What I mean is, would you die if you stopped moving?
Your days off are supposed to be used for resting.
If any of you catches a cold, I will kick your ass.
So what exactly are you doing here, Daichi?
I came to make sure the basketball team hadn't taken over our court.
Yeah, and their bouncy ball dreams.
Good grief.
For crying out loud.
Daichi?
Hey there!
Ikajiri!
I watched the finals on TV.
You guys were great.
Thanks, man.
What the heck?
Are you nervous?
Oh, yeah.
Like you wouldn't believe.
Just the fact that you guys beat Shira Torizawa and made it to the nationals is incredible.
There's no reason for you to feel any pressure.
So relax and go do your best.
Nah, just kidding.
I mean, I seriously need you to pull this off, Daichi.
I'll be sending you all the vibes, and everyone around here is watching you.
Oh.
Keep winning.
Win for my team, too.
You're right.
Of course I am.
I really shouldn't be so freaked out.
I have a team with me.
Oh, dude!
There it is!
The Skytree!
Hey, first we're going to drop our luggage off at the hotel.
Then we're going to the gym coach Nekomata booked for us, where we'll do some light warm-ups.
Listen up!
I'm sure you know this, but you're going to be on your best behavior.
Yes, sir!
All right, we're almost there.
Okay, guys, grab your stuff.
Thanks for the ride!
Oh!
For real?
This is our hotel?
Holy crap!
Oh, sweet!
We are definitely going to see a house ghost day in this place!
Let's all go exploring!
Yeah!
Yes, sir.
Bring it on!
Hey!
Come on!
You could have gotten that!
Yes, sir!
Is it me?
Or is the air kind of thin here?
Well, um, it's sea level, so...
Looks like our anxious Andys are already getting just a little bit antsy.
Yeah, I actually thought Hinata had finally managed to get his nerves under control.
But I guess we can't expect them to be totally calm right before their first national tournament.
Well, this is exactly what I've been treating tots onto all that beer for.
Everything's fine.
So, I have some that I want you guys to see.
Some info to review about our first opponent.
No, we don't need to do that right now.
What we're going to be watching is Taki Now Electronics' very own...
I'M AWESOME HIGHLIGHT VIDEO REEL!
This is a collection of all your very best plays.
Each and every one of you.
AWESOME!
Show me!
Oh, man!
That's so cool!
Oh, yeah!
This song!
This video is much higher quality than I was expecting!
And listen, did he give them each their own theme song for this?
Tatsan even took the time to interview everybody's family and friends.
Um...
I thought we'd be analyzing and breaking down opponents all the way up until game time.
Doing that won't help us at all if our own players can't go out there and play.
With the help of these videos and this music, they're going to see themselves performing at their very best.
Because visualization is an important part of victory.
Okay, listen up.
I gotta go have a meeting with Coach.
I want you to keep an eye on these troublemakers, Inoshita.
Sure thing.
We'll do.
Whoa, whoa!
What the heck?
I'm the vice-captain.
You're supposed to ask me.
Yeah.
You just encouraged them, so...
I don't think so.
You don't know.
Huh?
Kagayama, where are you going?
Out for a run.
I didn't get nearly enough exercise today.
I'm going with him.
Huh?
No, you can't.
You're the last two people I can let leave this hotel.
It's the wastelands of Tokyo out there.
But if they don't go and they can't get to sleep tonight, that would be bad, too.
Tsukushima!
No chance.
But I haven't said anything yet.
You were going to tell me to go with them, right?
I've seen you pacing around ever since we got here, okay?
You're nervous, too.
Do you honestly believe I can even keep up with those two?
Thank you very much.
Oh, no.
Use it all you need.
I'm just sorry it's a piece of junk.
We appreciate it.
When I say we're heading back,
we're heading back, got it?
Mm-hmm.
If you don't listen to me,
I'll find some place where it'll be impossible for you to find your way back and leave both of you there.
Because you dummies have no idea where you are.
Yeah, whatever.
Looks like some of the guys went out on a run.
I'm sure you could go with them.
No, thanks.
I'll feel much better if I just watch these videos.
You brought your homework here, Suga?
Yeah.
This is when I always try to study.
That's awesome.
How do you stay so calm?
Actually, the studying is kind of what's keeping me so calm.
It's the routine that comforts me.
Hey, Asahi.
How many more times are you going to watch everyone's little I'm Awesome video?
I just, I can't stop.
They're all so cool.
Like, holy crap.
These are my teammates.
It's so awesome.
You played right into Coach's hands.
Uh, okay, you guys.
What's going on?
Think about it.
Kyoko is somewhere in here taking her bath right this naked second.
You expect us to stay calm knowing that?
I'm not careful.
My focus from the I'm Awesome video will be wiped out by my fantasy.
Me too.
I'd say in your case, it doesn't matter which of those you have in your tiny heads.
I'm always so nervous when it's just the two of us.
I need to think of something to say.
I, so, um, I noticed before that you still wear black tights when you've got your summer uniform on.
Doesn't that get a little hot?
Uh.
Oh, gosh, I'm so sorry for imposing my ideas on your wardrobe.
I'm going for a ride.
Wait.
I have a lot of scars on my legs.
I started wearing tights to hide them, and then I guess I just got used to it.
But scars?
Yeah, I, I was on the track team and I ran hurdles.
Except what I really did was trip on them.
My arms and upper body didn't suffer too much, but I scratched up my legs pretty badly.
Hurdles, that is so cool!
So your scars are badges of honor!
Huh?
I'm so sorry!
Can't believe I said that!
Wait, I'm so sorry!
Actually, it's flattering to hear you call them that.
Huh?
The track team at my middle school was absolutely huge, and I've never been the best at talking to people.
I never got especially close to any of my younger teammates, either.
Even after I joined the Karasuno Volleyball Club, it was a full two years before I had a junior manager.
So you're basically the first person I've been able to talk to in any real way.
And well, I'm going to be graduating soon.
Tomorrow, after we win our first match, let's come back here for another bath.
Yeah!
The Haruko National High School Volleyball Championship, also known as the Spring Nationals.
It's considered by some to be the koshien of volleyball.
It's the most highly anticipated high school volleyball tournament of the year.
We're here!
The same stage where the Tiny Giant battled!
Well, the Tiny Giant you're talking about actually never competed here.
They played in Yo-Yogi back then.
Enough out of you!
Alright!
It has the same atmosphere and ambiance!
Can it be true?
Could this be the lucky incident of lechery I've always dreamed of?
Otherwise known as...
The Lucky Lecture?
I'm sorry.
There's nothing I can do to stop it.
Thank you, God.
Thank you, sweet Hinata.
Goodness, are you alright?
Yes, thanks!
I'm fine!
Hey, is that you, Kanaka?
Good to see you!
Hello, Ryu!
It's been so long!
Huh?
Are you telling me you know her?
Yeah!
She's a wing spiker for Niyama High!
How have you been?
Last time I saw you was fourth grade!
That's right.
I see you're just as big as, uh, ever!
She's...
Really matured.
Tanaka's brain has collapsed.
I did think it was kind of weird to see him talking to a girl like it was a normal thing.
Usually he would have already puked all over himself and fallen down.
He's embarrassing himself.
Anyway, good luck to both of us for you!
Uh, yeah, it's you!
Hey, Kageyama!
It's good to see you!
Oh, hey!
Check it out!
Looks like even Kageyama knows somebody here.
They must have met at that youth intensive.
I think that's Motoyakomori.
I saw him listed as the top liberal in monthly volleyball magazine.
Soksa didn't come here to the ceremony with you?
He's hiding over there.
Absolutely hates crowds.
I'm surprised he hasn't faded yet.
Hey, hey, hey!
Heal to my man!
Bokuto!
Well, well, it seems like my number one pupil made it here after all!
Hinata, when he's an ass, you can tell him to shut up.
That's Bokuto from Fukurodani.
The guy seems like kind of a nutjob.
And who's that shrimp that he called his number one pupil?
I still won't go easy on you when we're across the net.
Good!
Oh, sookie!
Hey, man!
Sookie, sookie!
Lookie, lookie!
Oh, did you get taller?
Oh, you can't get it, didn't you?
So, did you finally get a chance to see the real Skytree?
Country bumpkins.
We did.
Well, well, well.
Don't tell me you're getting nervous, my dear Daichin.
I believe you're talking too much is a sign of your nervousness, Kuro, my friend.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for your patience.
We will now begin the opening ceremonies for the Haruko National High School Volleyball Championship.
I ask you now to direct your attention to the main floor.
The championship flags are now entering the stadium.
Please welcome the teams representing each of the 47 prefectures of Japan.
From Hokkaido, first representative, Boyd.
We can't expect the boys to not be restless.
But you at least need to be calm, right, coach?
Yes, I know I am calm!
Blighter, second representative, Boyd, Morikawa High School, and the ladies.
Need the bathroom again?
No, I do not!
Miyagi Prefecture, representatives.
Boys, Karasuno High School.
Girls, Niyama Girls High School.
Fukushima Prefecture, representatives.
Boys, Furukata High School.
Girls, Iwaki Girls High School.
This is it.
It's the battle on the Orange Court!
play Mutta.
Address 06 becomes pride in219.
If you don't feel Eh Podian reopob disturbs, you need it.
Episode 8, 5,3 is not true.
exaggeration to inspire people and you know that.
仏li rei police in30 to 06.
Dena'sок MRT 3 is not fair, it could be complacent.
神様の助けはいらない
エゴイストそれがどうした
勝ちたいに理由などない
挑まずにはいられない
影さえも振り切ってけ
現状の限界なり越えろチャンス
戦力をかけた 怯えることない
隠しで変われ
高く高く高く舞い上がれ
味わった敗北の傷は
涙やって花を咲かせる
諦めろと笑えばいいさ
そんな言葉 僕は知らない
深など笑えばいいさ
Next time, Battle Lines